Caio Fukelmann Landau

Head of Mobile Development @ Mozio Group

Passionate engineer with over 8 years of experience. Android, iOS and frontend.

Assembled team of world-class developers with essentially zero turnover for 4+ years.

After working under Caio's leadership for almost 4 years, I can only speak wonders about him. Aside from being one of the best developers I've ever met, he is also an amazing boss and mentor [...]

- Matias Bzurovski, LinkedIn recommendation

Contact Information

email: caioflandau@gmail.com

https://linkedin.com/in/caioflandau

https://caiolandau.com/

https://angel.co/caioflandau

Personal Information

birthday: March 17th, 1991

born: São Paulo, SP - Brazil

Language Fluency

Portuguese

native

Enalish

fluent

Chinese Mandarin

learning

at **FIAP**

Education

Bachelor's Degree — 2010 - 2013 Computer Information Systems (similar to Computer Science)

Proficient

(and always improving!)

- Engineering project: technical structuring and planning
- Object-oriented programming
- Javascript
- Android Kotlin / Java
- iOS Swift / Objective-c
- TDD

Head of Mobile Development at Mozio Group

Remote – April 2016 - Today

Mozio is a global mobility platform offering worldwide ground transportation

Main responsibilities:

- Leading a team of 5 mobile engineers and 1 tech lead
- Mentoring and advocating for the team
- Hiring mobile engineers
- Promoting the engineering team culture
- Android (Java / Kotlin) and iOS (Swift) apps and SDKs

Mobile Engineer at Mozio Group

Remote — October 2014 - April 2016

Mozio is a global mobility platform offering worldwide ground transportation

Main responsibilities:

- Planning and executing Mozio's first mobile engineering project: the Mozio mobile app
- Developing Android (Java / Kotlin) and iOS (Swift) apps
- Developing native and Flutter apps
- Assembling Mozio's first team of mobile developers

(for past work experience: see page 2)

Intermediate

(still learning...)

- Engineering management
- Flutter
- React
- MQTT / RabbitMQ
- SQL / SQLite

Beginner

(a new journey starts!)

- React Native
 - AngularJS
 - Python

Past Work Experience

Mobile Developer (iOS and Android) - incube - December 2012 - October 2014

A venture builder in São Paulo, Brazil. http://www.incube.mobi/

Responsible for Android (Java) and iOS (Objective-c) development and multiple apps.

Web Developer Intern - iai - August 2011 - November 2012

iai was a developer shop and school in São Paulo, Brazil

Recently Published Work

Mozio SDK

This is an SDK that allows any developer to include a complete Mozio ride-booking experience inside their app. Available for both iOS and Android, the code is native - Kotlin and Swift:

• Documentation and details found here: https://developer.mozio.com/mobile-sdk/

Mozio native mobile apps

Native apps, written in Kotlin/Java and Swift:

- Android: https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.mozio.android
- iOS: https://apps.apple.com/us/app/mozio-airport-rides-taxis/id1103373539

Mozio driver apps

Those apps were developed with Flutter - a multi-platform library from Google:

- Android: https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.mozio.driver
- iOS: https://apps.apple.com/us/app/mozio-driver/id1436530159